[
  {
    "id": "493",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 3",
      "question": "Which of these CPU related metrics are available by default in CloudWatch?",
      "answers": [
        "CPUCreditBalance",
        "CPUCreditUsage",
        "CPUUtilization",
        "CPUOutageTime"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["CPUCreditBalance", "CPUCreditUsage", "CPUUtilization"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "494",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 4",
      "question": "Which of these Disk Usage related metrics are available by default in CloudWatch?",
      "answers": [
        "DiskReadBytes",
        "DiskReadOps",
        "DiskWriteBytes",
        "DiskWriteOps",
        "DiskReadErrors",
        "DiskWriteErrors"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["DiskReadBytes", "DiskReadOps", "DiskWriteBytes", "DiskWriteOps"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "495",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 4",
      "question": "Which of these Network Usage related metrics are available by default in CloudWatch?",
      "answers": [
        "NetworkIn",
        "NetwordOut",
        "NetworkPacketsIn",
        "NetworkPacketsOut",
        "NetworkPacketsError"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["NetworkIn", "NetwordOut", "NetworkPacketsIn", "NetworkPacketsOut"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "496",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 3",
      "question": "Which of these Status related metrics are available by default in CloudWatch?",
      "answers": [
        "StatusCheckFailed",
        "StatusCheckFailed_Instance",
        "StatusCheckFailed_System",
        "StatusCheckFailed_All",
        "StatusCheckFailed_Default"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["StatusCheckFailed", "StatusCheckFailed_Instance", "StatusCheckFailed_System"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "497",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Any metric you try to add to a CloudWatch dashboard that is not on the default list has to be added via a ___________?",
      "answers": [
        "Custom Metric",
        "Detailed Metric",
        "Status Metric",
        "Analysis Metric"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Custom Metric"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "498",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "CloudWatch standard monitoring checks and logs metrics every ______ metrics?",
      "answers": [
        "5 minutes",
        "1 minute",
        "10 minutes",
        "2 minutes"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["5 minutes"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "499",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "CloudWatch detailed monitoring checks and logs metrics every ______ metrics?",
      "answers": [
        "5 minutes",
        "1 minute",
        "10 minutes",
        "2 minutes"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["1 minute"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "500",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 4",
      "question": "Which of these can you create with CloudWatch?",
      "answers": [
        "Dashboards",
        "Alarms",
        "Events",
        "Logs",
        "Queries",
        "Audit Trail"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Dashboards", "Alarms", "Events", "Logs"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "501",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which of the CloudWatch features help you see everything that is happening within your AWS account?",
      "answers": [
        "Dashboards",
        "Alarms",
        "Events",
        "Logs",
        "Queries",
        "Audit Trail"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Dashboards"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "502",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which of the CloudWatch features allows you to send notifications when particular thresholds are hit?",
      "answers": [
        "Dashboards",
        "Alarms",
        "Events",
        "Logs",
        "Queries",
        "Audit Trail"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Alarms"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "503",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which of the CloudWatch features allows you to respond to state changes in your AWS resources?",
      "answers": [
        "Dashboards",
        "Alarms",
        "Events",
        "Logs",
        "Queries",
        "Audit Trail"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Events"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "504",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which of the CloudWatch features allows you to aggregate, monitor, and store logs?",
      "answers": [
        "Dashboards",
        "Alarms",
        "Events",
        "Logs",
        "Queries",
        "Audit Trail"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Logs"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "505",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which of these is for logging and monitoring?",
      "answers": [
        "CloudWatch",
        "CloudTrail"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Logs"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "506",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which of these is for creating an audit trail?",
      "answers": [
        "CloudWatch",
        "CloudTrail"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["CloudTrail"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "507",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which AWS service monitors your entire AWS account environment and creates an audit trail for your environment?",
      "answers": [
        "CloudWatch",
        "CloudTrail",
        "CloudFormation",
        "CloudFront"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["CloudTrail"]
    }
  }
]
